{"data":[{"question":"They never help their mother with the housework.     -> Their mother ...................... with the housework.\n","answer":"is never helped","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"The Robinsons keep their huge Rottweiler dogs in the garden.     -> Huge Rottweiler dogs............................ by the Robinsons in the garden.\n","answer":"are kept","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"Who won this match?     -> Who ...................... this match won by?\n","answer":"was","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"This company sell their products all over the world.     -> This company's products ........................ all over the world.\n","answer":"are sold","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"A Dutch scientist built the first pendulum clocks in 1656.     -> The first pendulum clocks ....................... in 1656 by a Dutch scientist.\n","answer":"were built","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"Maintenance engineers check regularly all the equipments.     -> All the equipments .................. regularly by maintenance engineers.\n","answer":"are checked","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"They awarded Mother Teresa the Nobel Peace Prize in 1979.     -> Mother Teresa ................. the Nobel Peace Prize in 1979.\n","answer":"was awarded","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"Women fans send thousands of letters to Antonio Banderas every month.     -> Thousands of letters ................ to Antonio Banderas every month.\n","answer":"are sent","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"His elder brother taught him how to ride a bike.     -> He ............................ how to ride a bike by his elder brother.\n","answer":"was taught","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"The mechanic didn't repair my car on time.     -> My car ....................... on time by the mechanic.\n","answer":"wasn't repaired","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"}]}